(Leonard:)Hey, what's up?
(Howard:)I need a place to crash.
(Leonard:)Uh, sure.
(Leonard:)Why?
(Howard:)Big fight with my mother.
Still arguing over
which CSI is the best?
(Howard:)No, we agreed they all have
their merits.
(Howard:)This was about Bernadette.
(Sheldon:)What's going on?
(Leonard:)Howard's gonna sleep here
tonight.
(Leonard:)He had a fight with his mother.
(Sheldon:)Did you offer him
a hot beverage?
(Bernadette:)No.
(Sheldon:)Leonard, social protocol states
when a friend is upset,
(Sheldon:)you offer them a hot beverage,
such as tea.
(Howard:)Tea does sound nice.
(Sheldon:)You heard the man, Leonard.
(Sheldon:)And while you're at it,
I'm upset
(Sheldon:)that we have an unannounced
houseguest, so make me cocoa.